hey how's it going folks this is Ryan
Perez owner and founder of the hustle
Zone how's everyone doing today I know I
haven't been doing much uh live
streaming uh we've just been uh uh
putting a lot of energy in building this
magazine I want to uh shout out to all
the contributors uh so that's Jason
Daniels Anthony mladen hen Jamie Lynn uh
we have Mark and Carla elk Hill and
Shantel Lee and Ricardo McCrae so I give
a big shout out to those content
creators we're still looking for for
Content creators uh folks so please make
sure to hit me up in my DMs um uh there
are some requirements you you do have to
sign some agreements Etc so be prepared
for that we're not just looking for
anybody but um you know just hit me up
and and let me know if you're interested
and I'll send you all the information in
details so yes so yeah it has been uh
it's been it's been a while I want to
first uh shout out to Philip Woods uh
get that
tea you see the uh the sweater here so
make sure you guys pick up your hustle
Zone uh sweaters the link is in the
description so at uh hustle
zone. and then you can get yourself um a
hoodie you probably don't want a hoodie
right now uh you probably want to get we
do have te's lady te's and we do have
T-shirts and all kind of good stuff and
if you don't see something there that
you like please let me know and I will
uh and will design it because I'm a
designer yes so anyway uh so folks
magazine like I said is being launched
on September 1st so this is a digital
magazine and I want to emphasize because
I think I kind of like with the last few
lives that I've had I need to emphasize
the the importance of what we're doing
we're not just doing any old visual
magazine we're actually talking about
the lives and stories of entrepreneurs
you know this is we are defining
entrepreneurialism as a culture because
you know what we do every day everybody
like I guess everyone's different we all
have different paths
but at the end of the
day these paths are all pretty similar
in terms of habits you know um a lot of
us go to bed late we wake up early we
grind we hustle um you know a lot of us
are very cautious about what we put in
our in our bodies in terms of food you
know the type of people that we surround
ourselves with you know the fact that we
read Self Health books we we pop that CD
in the car or I guess not CD nowadays
but you know your iPod and and and
whatnot listening to audiobooks so
there's a lot of cultural practices that
we all engage in but we don't
necessarily see that as a cultural
practice I think that you know I I I'm
going to be as bold to say that it is a
cultural practice and that um you know
if we we if we want to encourage more
people to be entrepreneurs we kind of
have to pass that knowledge down and it
seems like with this
this this craze with face live and all
these social uh influencers uh coming
out of the Woodworks it seems like
everybody's just you know everyone's
kind of adding their two cents and
there's and and we're all watching it
all happen there's not enough content
we're always you know engaging um in in
watching new people and listening to new
stuff reading new books because we just
want to be immersed in this culture so
um I I do want to stress that that's why
you want to support the hustle Zone our
our slogan is rep the culture um so
we're to we're taking a completely
different spin um to all of this we're
not just talking about
lifestyle you know we're talking about
everything else we're expanding the crop
because you know you can watch the Ty
lopezes of the world you can watch uh
Gary Vee you can watch Grant cardones
and they're very successful it's awesome
but there's a lot of the stuff that they
don't show you that I want to be able to
show you via the hustle zone so um you
know we've been doing this almost a year
now like doing the actual interviewing
for almost a year under the hustle Zone
Banner so I'm you know I'm super excited
for um our our guest
tonight you know him and I has spoken um
a few times and um I'm so glad and and
even honored that he reached out to to
want to be a part of the show you know
he's he's a guy let me tell you he a guy
you actually want to follow
okay he's a guy that you want to follow
because he has his he has his poop in
the group you know he has he has his
[ __ ] together um and I really appreciate
the level of you know like he has he go
on if you go on his Pages you know there
he has nice memes and you know he has
everything lined up and put together and
it seems like he's linning himself with
with great people and he's really
producing great cont content for for for
for folks um so and he's a younger guy
younger than me but you know I I would
say that he's he's he's um he's someone
that I can admire uh for all the things
that he is doing and so I'm super to I'm
super happy to have him so let's get
right into it since we're late and I I
apologize I know it's supposed to be
9:00 but I had some
technical te te te technical issues um
but uh let's uh say hello to Brandon
Adams how's it going my friend it's
going great man I I by the way I love
hustle hustle Zone you know
entrepreneurs have to hustle at the
beginning they have to grind to see any
success it's not going to be easy you
know that's right that's right and I
mean you've you've done a lot of
hustling and and um how long have you
been doing this for by the
way since I was
born no I I've been grinding my whole
life man I uh for what I do online is
honestly only been four four years 3 to
four years hardcore uh kind of got in
this started in this kind of world and
five years ago but my whole life I I
grew up as an entrepreneur my dad he
sold uh ice Artic Glacier they're
actually based out of Canada and uh he
owns a distributorship of them and I
worked in that business my whole life
growing up and I end up acquiring that
from him three years ago so actually fun
little fact about me is I own a
brick-and motor business Beyond online
so I know what it's like to actually run
a tangible business with trucks
employees insurance and headaches nice
nice well you know what Arctic Glacier
um was a kind of mine um really like
when I was in the I was selling cell
phones uh to corporate companies and uh
there was an Arctic Glacier is actually
a couple of blocks down from my house so
I used to go there to to get them all
lined up with their blackberries and
that is so funny because I when I worked
at I used to work for the corporate side
of things and I actually negotiated the
cell phone deal for my whole division
the state of Iowa which is like 50
phones but I always wanted I never went
to Canada I've never been in Canada and
one of my Dan Dan lawren lawrel I
haven't talked in a while a good friend
of mine that's in Canada and he he like
I don't know he probably works the
location that's right next to you
yeah I think I I I don't remember the
names but because it was like a while
back but you know I I like I was driving
past AR Arctic uh uh glaci just the
other day and I was like yeah man like
that's what I was starting out I was a
little young pup you know doing my sales
and stuff so yeah interesting company
yeah but um but either way let's um so
normally what I I I normally ask every
one of my my my guests that come on to
the show uh um is pretty much what is
your story so dial it back bring me back
from the beginning and move your way up
we want to know everything we want to
know who you are as as a person ice I
sell ice to
Eskimos literally no seriously man um my
beginning was dice business I my dad
started the company in ' 86 he he worked
for a guy he bought the company out and
I was born in ' 89 n and basically what
I did my whole life is worked in that
business and got to see what it was like
to to run a business and uh my whole
life working with him I learned the ins
and outs of of business working with
customers uh people that didn't pay uh
the the parts where trucks broke down
and it was stressful and I got to see
that so I did go to college and I always
said one day I wanted to buy out the ice
business from my father and I graduated
from college I graduated end up well
first owning a percentage of the company
and then end up uh two years later
acquiring the company from him but uh in
that business one day and this kind of
where my journey
began is I I was delivered ice one day
and it was really hot and I wanted to
keep a bottle beverage cold and it's
timec consuming to put ice cubes in the
bottle beverage I wanted something fit
in easily but also be able little flavor
a drink that day I I came up this idea
called the Arctic stick
and I it's a product that cools and
flavors your drink I spent the next
three and a half years of my life
putting a lot of money into developing
this product and I mean I was selling
real estate in the weekends I had a real
estate license I was selling ice I was
basically anything I made went to this
and even for a while I actually worked
in corporate uh working for the company
Artic Glacier so we owned a
distributorship so that was a different
side of things but I also like wanted to
learn more so I went and worked for the
company we bought our product from
and I one time I was managing eight
locations and and 50 employees and at I
was 22 at the time and most people were
twice or three times my age that I was
managing and it was an interesting
experience but I I learned a lot from
that and uh but where things kind of led
to where I'm at today in online world is
this invention Artic stick I was
obsessed with it it was my baby my idea
I put a 100 Grand into this invention
and I I put everything into it but I
learned marketing I learned I started
doing like commercials I learned how to
be in front of a camera all these things
I learned and and for anybody listening
just so you know at the beginning those
things you learn in that process are
what help you in the future and on my
last leg of funding for Artic stick I
did a Kickstarter campaign I did a
crowdfunding campaign and I thought okay
I can go on this Kickstarter and raise a
bunch of money I saw this guy that did
the potato salad did he raised 50 grand
for a potato salad
and it was hard man like it was the
hardest thing I ever did in a month or
33 days we raised 26 Grand which is
pretty good but it wasn't huge I learned
that I didn't know [ __ ] about
crowdfunding and I I wanted to solve the
problem like any entrepreneur I wanted
to solve this problem so what I did is
that next year I committed to becoming
the best in the industry I started
interviewing people I started traveling
the country uh I started a podcast show
myself called uh Liv to grind I uh I
also was uh helping other people with
with crowdfunding just to get my kind of
feet wet get myself in the system I end
up wrting a book called keys to the
crowd unlocking the power crowdfunding
and this is back in by the way
2015 and I went on a tour across the
country going on TV and I was promoting
local crowdfunding campaigns I was
building my brand is what I was doing
but you wanted me to talk about the
hustle so when I did this I I had a F1
50 pickup and I was driving across the
country I once did a 10-day trip from De
Mo to California and around and to
Albuquerque Phoenix and back to De Moine
for less than a thousand bucks I slept
in my truck and I slept in my truck a
lot that year because I was
bootstrapping anything I had I looked at
it this way if I I could spend $19 or
100 bucks on a hotel room or I could
sleep in my truck and not spend any
money and put that money into Facebook
ads and that was my mentality because I
I I was bootstrapping I really want to
invest everything I had into my business
and so I I where things changed for me
is during one of my interviews I had
John le Dumis entrepreneur fire on my
podcast show and one thing that I do
that's differently than I mean at the
end of every show I find a way to help
somebody I find a way to partner with
that person well it turned out jld had
this idea to do a book launch for a book
called the Freedom Journal and he told
me that and I said well hey I'm a
crowdfunding expert I was still like
trying to be seen as an expert I didn't
really know exactly what I was doing but
uh took that campaign on and we raised a
half a million dollars in a month we
made it the fifth largest crowd fitting
campaign in history for a book and after
that so-called overnight success and
we're talking like literally a year of
grind sleep in my truck and not making
any money um to to raise at a half a
million dollars in a month was was huge
so that led basically that success
attracted other people and that year I
ended up doing a campaign with Kevin
Harrington the original shark of shark
tank we we crowdfunded his book put a
shark your tank um we did a campaign for
thinking go Rich the Legacy we actually
crowdfunded the the bestselling book
thinking Rich by Napoleon Hill we crowd
footed docky drama raised $365,000 in a
couple months for that and uh we I even
crowd footed my own TV show so I end up
using using crowdfunding as a way to not
only drive my own companies but to to be
able to get myself into positions to be
a part of some cool things and make some
money in the process so crowdfunding was
my way and again just to show the
journey I'm a guy that sold ice for a
living I still do but I mean not my
day-to-day anymore but I sold ice I had
an
invention I I spent $100,000 on an
invention a product that I didn't make
hardly anything back on but that
$100,000 lesson was the best education I
could have got because I learned
marketing I learned crowdfunding it led
me to crowdfunding which allowed me to
raise last year $1.5 million for our
clients and also to be a part of three
companies so that was my beginning and I
guess that was kind of the grind and
most people like oh I can't believe you
spent so much money on that product well
if I didn't do that I wouldn't be where
I'm at today with working with these
people and having my own TV show and all
these opportunities but it was a grind
man and my biggest motto along the way
was just keep going just keep going It's
a Grind every single day and I mean even
when you have the good moments and
something will kick you in the ass and
you'll find an opportunity like
something else will happen to you and
what really defines a successful
entrepreneur and a average or
unsuccessful entrepreneur is the
successful one never quits and they
never give up and they know that they're
going to be successful even when they're
in the toughest [ __ ] when they're bank
accounts negative or they're in a point
of your life where it's hard they know
they're going to succeed they already
know they just know that that's part of
the
journey interesting so
how I guess there's so much information
out there in regards to to learning how
to Crow fund so how did you decipher
what was you know what was great and
what was not great and where where did
you kind of develop your formula in yeah
in in crowdfunding so so I just I I
spent hours upon hours going on
kickstarter.com and looking all the
campaigns and what did they have in
common what did the like the ones that
succeeded what was the common Trend the
ones that failed what was the common
Trend and then I also interviewed
experts so I interviewed um a guy named
Chris Hawker he's a good friend now and
he he has a company called and design
where they they helped design the
coolest cooler that raised 13.2 million
and like he had done many campaigns he
had a key campaign he did a carbon flyer
so I interviewed him and learned from
him and I interviewed other successful
people I mean that's what I always say
interview somebody that's already
achieved what you want to achieve and
just F in their Footsteps in your own
way so I did that and uh what that what
that led to is just learning but then
how I really learn man is just by doing
you learn by doing you have to do I I
did campaigns and a couple of our first
ones like we raised not much money we
had one we raised like 177,000 another
one then we we rais half a million then
rais 300 and something thousand like you
just got to keep going and you get
better as you go in every campaign I
learned something unique and I learned
from now like we work with big
influencers because here's what happens
so I have a formula for crowdfunding
it's the acronym fund I wrote a whole
book on this called keys to the crowd
unlocking the power of crowdfunding and
it is uh f is forethought U is utilized
marketing plan n is narrative and D is
deliver value f for thought you got to
prepare for your campaign ahead of time
45 to 60 days to prepare for the launch
to prepare for everything you're going
to do most people just show up and they
think it's going to happen it's like are
you going to show for a marathon and
just run it without any training no and
so you got to prepare um utilize
marketing plan you got to do more than
just share you got to do Facebook ads
you have to go on podcast shows you have
to get articles to write blog about you
you got to get publicity you have to get
JV Partnerships email list all these
things uh the narrative aspect like
anything else you got to tell a great
story your campaign has to tell a great
story through a video that you create
through the copy that you create
storytelling and then deliver value your
offer on a crowdfunding platform has to
be something that people want and it's
like they get something in return
they're not just donating most people
think oh I'm just going to donate no
you're actually pre-ordering products
the people that hire me now
they're their celebrities or
millionaires they they're hiring me to
use crowdfunding as a platform to launch
their products
so that those steps are what you follow
to have success in crowdfunding that's
what I teach and that's what I've
learned and uh it's been a fun ride but
I also apply those steps for anything in
life for anything that I do prepare for
your success Market tell a grade story
and deliver value if you do that in
business you're going to have success
that's all fine and dandy but uh you
know a lot of people think that it's
just an easy let me get a clickfunnels
campaign and launch and and and whatnot
so uh tell me a little bit like I and
I'm not knocking click funnels because I
I think it it does do well for some
people but I think that um yeah we use
it you guys use clickfunnels yeah so but
you have to there's so much work that
goes into a lot of these camp
um
and how how do how do you uh how do you
address a lot of the the the the
internet marketers that are just kind of
flying at the seat of their
pants I mean for me it is a lot of work
and I tell a clients right now we're
very we've learned from taking on the
just some campaigns that at the time
were just we took on we didn't we were
still learning but now like we only work
with celebrities influencers we let them
know up front like it's a it's a grind
and even if you have an audience the the
audience might not react to your offer I
mean it's like an infomercial industry
Kevin Harrington is a mentor of mine and
I mean he said for the infomercial
industry nine out of 10 products fail
and again it's industry you don't know
what's going to work and what isn't and
you look at and I like for clickfunnels
actually was just started reading
Russell brunson's book um expert secrets
and he said he's done thousands of
Trials and Air
to be able to get to the point where the
offer is just right and nobody not
everybody shares like you said not
everybody shares the failures and I like
to share the failures all day um for our
campaigns and the ones we've had
successful here's what it it consisted
of it consisted of multiple people
spending hundreds of hours combined on a
project and spending thousands of
dollars on Facebook ads and different
ads and and asking favors and doing
strategic Partnerships and basically
working non-stop during the campaign to
make it succeed that's what it takes if
you think you're going to just launch a
campaign you're GNA put it up and you're
going to put a a a button where people
will pay you they're not going to just
give you money because nobody gives a
[ __ ] they want to know what's in it for
me and you have to be in front of them
if they don't know what you have and
what you have to offer they don't know
to give you money and it's hard in this
world you're seeing Facebook ads every
day it's like goldfish like literally
ads going up and down and up and down
and the people that stand out are the
ones that are really trying to help you
there's a lot of [ __ ] out there and
clutter but adding a lot of value
literally showing value and I just
interviewed a guy uh Michael Devin shout
out to him great guy he just came on my
show and he said sell results literally
just sell results and your own results
and your own business and I show
literally what we're doing the success
and failures and they see well this is
real life this is what we've done for
people and he's done that believe it or
not this is so interesting Facebook like
if they heard this like holy [ __ ] he his
business he launched he added so much
value to his audience Michael and on his
personal Facebook P page he offered this
course it's a $3,000 course it was for
Amazon users in 48 hours he did close to
half a million dollars in sales and just
pushing out his personal page he didn't
spend a dime in in marketing um but how
he did that was because he spent
months upon months offering value to the
audience without asking anything
return so so what I my point of that is
I believe if you want to stand out in
anything and you just got to add so much
value so many people are looking to get
a quick make a quick Buck you have to
build relationships before you can
actually turn that into Revenue so let
let me ask you I
mean what does
if if you you like I deal with a lot of
coaches okay there's there's a lot of
coaches and it's a highly saturated
market so uh you can't tell the coach to
say hey get out of this business this is
not for you um because that would be
that's just not right right that's this
is their passion and you know we're
taught to live our passions every
day but in your case what would you
recommend these coaches do in terms of
bringing value if they're all competing
in the same
space I
mean here's my belief and the coach
thing
like I don't ever like to be called a
coach because I mean I do sell like
accelerator programs and people pay high
dollar to go in them but I I I offer
more than just like pure advice like
tangibles accountability all that but
this is why I believe this is why I
create videos all the time and why we
have a podcast show and magazine and and
build
influence I believe people buy from
people so if you can put out enough
valuable content to the audience
non-stop
content what'll happen is eventually
people will buy from you and I can tell
you out all the coaches out there I
guarantee you maybe a small percentage
of them are doing constant video content
out there where they're adding value to
Their audience free value and the ones
that are creating content and adding
free value and advice to Their audience
somebody might not buy from at that
moment but down the road they may buy
from them because that person's in front
of them so if you are yep but I mean
like this is a business where you know
some people have mortgaged their homes
some people just got out of school they
got their coaching degree um they need
to make money so they're not going to
wait for you know for people to convert
over to them you know they they want to
see results like ASAP so you
know what do you say to that yeah
so I'm a millennial you're a millennial
too um so some Millennials get the bad
like some people give us a bad name and
they're like oh Millennials they want
something they want everything given to
them and and stuff but then people like
you and I like I I've earned everything
I've got I have no inheritance I I've
[ __ ] grinded for the [ __ ] that I have
and I can tell you horror stories all
day or literally and I will share them
like [ __ ] have went through but um it
doesn't happen overnight you got to have
patience uh you do have to have patience
like again I just talking buddy early
he's a millionaire and I said I'm
frustrated I'm I'm not a millionaire yet
we've done seven figures of Revenue but
I'm not a millionaire yet and I'm 27
years old and I'm like [ __ ] I wanted to
get there at 26 but I got to realize
it's patience it's a long journey it
doesn't happen overnight and so many
people what happens is and here's a bad
set of things they see a tilou and I
I've been at tiop as this place I've
spent two and a half hours on a webinar
with 60,000 people live I've been at gr
I've been at all the influencers places
and I've been on their shows and they
are inspiring people but also there is
this bad side of things where people see
them and they think I can come become
that overnight I can tell you grant
cardone's I think 50 years old Gary
vanderchuck's 4
I mean all these people Ty Lopez he's 52
by the way you won't share that with
anybody but these people
are they've been through a lot and
people see them they're like oh that
just happened overnight they they don't
see everything they went through they
just see where they're at now and
they're like I want to become a Ty Lopez
overnight it doesn't happen you have to
have patience you got to be willing to
be in the journey and that's why so many
people they want overnight success
there's no [ __ ] overnight success
it's overnight success yours in the
making you have to go through a grind
and every true entrepreneur has a story
to tell and if you're actually like
making money and and and being able to
like have a business going you're gonna
share some stories again you have to go
through the grind nothing you get
nothing for nothing you got to earn it
yeah and I you know that is my motto and
it's always been um especially when
people when when I send a a proposal to
um to to to somebody that needs a quote
and they're like whoa it costs that much
like yeah it it pretty much does cuz it
justifies the the price it's not like
you know because I mean you could charge
anything you could charge $1,000 you
could charge $10,000 you could charge
you know uh $25,000 it doesn't negate
the fact that you still have to put in
that work right because um and there's a
lot of thought that goes into it because
I mean when you're pouring in that money
you you definitely want to see some sort
of Roi yeah you know you you do you
definitely want to move forward um but
it it does take an investment and it
really does take you know and I I don't
always believe in testing things out
because I I think that if you if you if
you have a great mind frame and and um
or mindset but also are really good at
looking at um you know competition and
what's already out there so that you're
not building some sort of product that
is redundant I think that you can you
can definitely succeed but I think a lot
of people just spin the wheels and and
um you know and they don't really see
the value in pouring money into um into
these campaigns I mean you go to you got
to invest yourself again looking back
invested $100,000 into our product
and that that wasn't a loss I learned a
lot from that whole journey I I've paid
a consultant I I paid a manufacturer i'
I've got prototypes like I I learned
from all that I've spent a lot of money
in my brand I've traveled the country
and the one thing I really invested in
was my personal brand and you have to
invest in yourself I think you are your
number one product you just got to be
smart you're going to get burned along
the way I mean you do enough deals
you're going to get burned it just it's
inevitable if you think you're not going
to then you're not making enough
decisions and but uh just learn from it
pivot learn don't let it like discourage
you and then move forward and don't make
this same mistake
twice um cuz it seems like the narrative
that you're pitching seems like you just
have it all together like you just no
you know like so I'll share a good story
with you so here's a good one for you
2014 uh I left corporate left the
corporate job and at that time I had
just had uh actually I just bought my
dad's company so I bought it out from
him
um and I left my full-time job and I
went to go pursue a company so I had
Artic sck but I was going to go start a
product development company I had three4
of a million dollars lined up in
investment uh I told my girlfriend at
the time who's with me now we've been
through a journey to quit her fulltime
job to start and work with me we got
apartment uh signed lease signed we got
the office picked out we uh literally
picked everything out and we moved to
the company I was all in I burned the
bridges man I went all in and the last
minute basically the deal fell through
and I I turned on the money so I went
from thinking I was going to have 750
Grand and all these things that start a
company to we had a lease to pay for we
had no [ __ ] money my girlfriend left
her job for me and we had nothing and
I'm like what the [ __ ] am I going to do
it's probably the lowest point in my
life and uh so I learned from that what
I learned is when you hit rock bottom
you figure out you do have human powers
to like move forward and and you you can
survive it's your our minds are survival
mode uh I realized
that at that point that you don't get
the million dollars overnight it's not
fairy tales it's not just going to
happen you have to actually work for it
and I made a pivot I I ped for a week
and I was pissed and then I I made a
pivot and what I did is I went to what I
knew I went back to Artic stick we did a
crowdfunding campaign we raised 26 Grand
in a month had some cash flow I learned
from that and I was going for a while
month to month and I was trying new
things I didn't know how to make money I
was like how do I how do I get paid um
and I was doing modeling gigs I was
doing uh commercials to pay the bills
and I was just doing this to to to baild
make sure the lights were turn on and
some people thought I was more
successful than I was but I was really
just grinding nonstop to support a
business and another business and one
business was feeding the other to make
sure it doesn't go under and so I
learned from that and then after I
started getting some deals under my belt
and and making some money I I I it was
easier but then when money comes
problems come too uh there would be
deals that went wrong it it it didn't
work out so I can tell you things aren't
all together uh even now I mean there's
still things that come at me there's
fires to put out I I do deals and
somebody's not happy or something goes
wrong I mean again when you make enough
decisions on a daily basis you're going
to have problem s you're going to have
things you have to deal with uh
so it's not all perfect uh but I I I am
putting things in the right direction
and and definitely I think back on that
story when I basically lost it all and
my girlfriend I let her down because I
basically told her she you're all right
babe and I go from oh hey we have to
find jobs and we didn't work jobs she
actually looked at working at bar and
she didn't she got into fitness and now
she's online personal trainer for me
I just did some modeling acting I I
worked the ice like I I did what what
got me through so it's not all rainbows
uh and see most people aren't willing to
do that man you know that story people
move to a city and they're like oh dude
you lost it all like most people would
fold [ __ ] that I don't fold nothing will
ever stop me the only thing that stopped
me is the Bullet to the Head like I will
never stop and that's why I've been able
to have great opportunities I'm
definitely young I got many years to go
but I can tell you what defines and all
the people I've interviewed defines a
successful entrepreneur and a person
that's average which average [ __ ]
average like literally what defines them
is the successful entrepreneur never
quits when they face temporary failure
you're going to have obstacles and
they're going to be there just learn how
to get around them solve the problem
sounds like Think and Grow Rich to me it
seems like you're reading a page out of
Think and Grow Rich but every day my
friend every day I mean but you you're
so right and I I had this conversation
um just the another day I was just doing
a random live on my camera cleaning up
my house and um I was like that's the
spirit of the entrepreneur it's like you
first have to believe that you could do
something I mean yeah you know that's
the it takes you got to have that belief
in yourself and if whether we're
narcissistic or not um you know you have
to have that quality otherwise you won't
succeed but the second thing I said is
that you need to be able you like when
when you start this grind or you start
this this journey you can't quit you
know and that you know the whole thing
about quitting because people get really
discouraged when you say
hey you can't quit because they're like
what that means I'm tied to this no
you're not tied to it it's just a
vehicle like any opportunity that you're
working on is a vehicle to get you from
where you want to be because if someone
said hey what do you want to be when you
grow up I just I want to be on the beach
siing dare man like I don't want to be
working but you know um but I'll I'll
find many different vehicles to get to
where I'm going to get and sometimes you
got to dial back cuz maybe someone died
in your family knock on wood or maybe uh
you you know like someone hit my car the
other day and it was written off so I
have to buy a new car so obviously you
know it was a loss it was a loss
financially to me but it it's still it's
still not a
um it's not a it's it's not going to
stop me from from getting at my my dream
right it I I feel like the the whole
quitting attitude I think the not
quitting attitude it really kind of
takes a load off your shoulders because
that means there's no time between you
and you reaching your goal as long as
you're on that pathway you're
fine just know that the feelings you
have don't let the emotions get to you
because you will have some time it's
like part of you goes like I just give
up but you're not going to just get
through the tough times and push through
and and take a break like take a step
back be like okay I'll get through this
and literally like for me you have a bad
day you wake up the next day you're good
to go um you just got to keep going so
many people don't dwell on the past
don't dwell on negative things that
happen just think of the positive
everything cuz you you have great
leadership um Quality
you know in your
mannerisms and and and whatnot and
you've obviously have different Ventures
going on so you're you're obviously a a
born leader but where did you pick those
skill sets up yeah um Thinking gich by
Napoleon Hill that book uh really made
me think I saw what Henry Ford and
Andrew Carnegie Thomas Edison all these
people have done and I saw they just
they didn't quit they they knew what
they wanted and they built a team around
them a mastermind and they kept going
and I just I've really just lived that
that principle in my life those
principles and that's how I take on
everything just don't quit how am I any
different than Thomas Edison how am I
any different than Andrew carne or Henry
Ford I'm not I can achieve that and
people like and a lot of people by the
way along the journey like people look
at me like you're [ __ ] crazy like
okay kid you're all talk and then I
started seeing success like oh he's
doing it no I I'm just and that's why
I'm all about live to grind hustle
zone I'll out work somebody a lot of
people can talk I will do I mean I it's
it's going to be midnight here I go on
another show until 1:00 am wake up
tomorrow and I do it again it's but I
enjoy it I love it so I think anything's
possible and that's what I got out of
that book and that's the mindset I've
always had and I've always been very
competitive I played rugby I played
football I always wanted to win I always
wanted to be the best me and I always
look in the mirror and think about how
can I get better how can I beat that guy
in the mirror today how could I make
myself
better so we I I do see that the clock
is it's uh almost 10 uh 10 p.m. over
here so yeah I forget the time zone yeah
almost minute here yeah yeah you're two
hours ahead um but I'll go into second
line of questioning I and again folks I
apologize for starting this late um it
it was just just I kind of changed the
setup a little bit I had some CPU issues
I had uh you know I could not find like
I had a brain fart couldn't find the
audio but we're here and this well
that's a grind man that's good though
because that needs to happen that's
that's the entrepreneurship if it was
all good then what's the fun in that
that's right that's right and and I
think this is this is actually the most
fruitful uh hustle Zone that I've had I
mean I've had great guests but you you
definitely uh
I would buy your books I would listen to
you talk because you actually seem like
you you you figured it out but I I don't
again I'm I figured things out Ryan but
I'm still figuring things out I'm human
like I got [ __ ] that's going wrong but I
I'm not afraid to share it I don't I
don't give a [ __ ] if people like what if
I'm going to share what I think and I do
this on my podcast show every week I
share just the truth and authenticity is
what people want I'm I'm a guy from a
farming community in a town of 750
people that just like tells it how it is
I'm not a city boy I'm I and I don't
think anybody I don't care what uh level
somebody's at whether they're a
billionaire they're a celebrity they're
a star or they're uh a janitor or a
waitress or waiter everybody deserves
respect and and I don't that's how I
look at things and I I never nobody
should ever look down upon anyone and I
just feel like success in my mind SU
success is being the best you and some
people see money as success yes I like
making a lot of money but what I think
is what is your definition of
success what is it for you what is it
for me it's different for everybody but
my thing is just be the best you whether
it's being the best mom the best dad the
best athlete the best actor the best
entrepreneur the best person on camera
every morning I wake up I stay a warrior
chant and I basically chant in the
mirror screaming about I am the most
successful Entre this time I will not
accept thefe I will not accept failure
whatever my mind conceives and believes
my mind achieves and I I I am great on
TV I'm the top influencer of the
Millennials I say this in the mirror and
I hit my chest and I get ready like I'm
going into war but that's my chant and
again I'm the best on camera that's my
what I say so success is being the best
you and and it's all mindset I know a
lot of people say mindset but it is it's
seriously it starts with your mind like
what you think you can do whatever your
mind conceives and believes it does do
it
achieves this was awesome um let's get
to the second um part of questioning
here and it's just a quick lightning
round uh just to lighter questions here
I mean this was a light interview but
still because normally I go deeper but I
didn't have enough time this time uh but
regardless you still got 9 minutes you
got plent time so what's your favorite
dessert oh man I like I like shakes uh
strawberry or chocolate uh Shake is
really good or cookie dough ice cream
cookie dough ice cream I love cookie
dough ice cream I think that's amazing
or birthday
cake nice uh what's your favorite TV
show what do you like to watch and don't
say that you don't watch T I know people
if you don't watch TV you're probably
watching Netflix or downloading a
torrent so I'll tell you I'll tell you
this I even from a TV host TV Creator I
don't watch TV but I do every once a I
watch Netflix and what I do like and if
you're an entrepreneur you would
appreciate this black mirr um actually I
got referred that I spent a day with
Perry Chang the founder of Kickstarter
and he's like dude you got to watch
black mirr so I watched it and it's just
crazy it's basically showing you what
our near future is going to be and it's
it's really here um it just advanced
technology and makes me think about
ideas for the future of business and
everything else so black Mir and I was
watching Limitless for a while I thought
that was pretty cool Limitless is
awesome um yeah what uh what's your
biggest pet
peeve I
hate people when they're all know it all
they think they know it all and they
like they do no wrong like they won't
ever admit like I admit when I [ __ ] up
because I [ __ ] up a lot but like they
won't admit they're wrong or people that
think that they're better than everybody
else and I don't care who you are your
[ __ ] don't stink like you you're not
better than I don't care who any
everybody should treat people with
respect no matter whether you got a
dollar in the bank account or you got a
100 million in the bank account what
what brings you the most
Joy TV video helping others speaking on
stage makes me feel alive um creating
content for others when they reach out
to me and they're like Brandon you
change my life that that that makes
really worth all the [ __ ] that I do
awesome Michael Jackson or
Prince that's a good one
um I don't
know Michael Prince maybe Prince okay
Nirvana or Foo
Fighters Foo
Fighters and um what if what would your
legacy be you know like again knock on
what you you know um if people had to
remember you what would they remember
you
for remember me for passion giving and
trying to make the biggest impact in
people's lives I want them to remember
me as someone that wanted to do the best
and most that he could possibly do to
help others on Earth that's I want them
remembers that and if you had a time
machine you can go back and talk to your
old self what would you tell that self
your younger
self create audience quicker start
creating non-stop video content and I
would have created a podcast show five
years
ago really yeah so create an audience so
like how how would you do that create
consistent content that's what I do now
uh create if you like to write do a Blog
every day if you like podcasting create
a podcast show every day or a couple
times a week videos create videos every
day um do something that puts out
content where you can build your own
audience and influence because if you
can build up your own audience influence
they can help you create your your
dream and they can fund it that's right
that's right uh so uh and let us know
where can we find
you yeah find me on liv.com you can find
our podcast show we got our our TV show
coming out uh all of our online
education but uh leave to . or SnapChat
me BT
adams8 I love Snapchat every single day
nice well thank you so much uh Adam for
coming on to the hustle zone so there is
a tradition before you leave um I I I'm
I'm compiling a video of all of this but
um it's a call and response so I'm going
to say welcome to the and you need to
scream hustle Zone as loud as you can
like you got to wake up the neighbors
and everything so uh okay I'll do it
I'll try to do it l my girlfriend's
sleep in the other room but we'll just
say you on the hustle zone so all right
so one two three welcome to the hustle
show okay hustle Zone okay we need to
get this right let's start this I said
right hustle Zone you said
show I said Zone and Zone you said show
I'll do it again okay one two 3 welcome
to the hustle Zone
oh I love it thank you so much and uh I
apologize to your girlfriend um I I'll
I'll tell her that you made me
yell but U so but yeah thank this is I'm
gonna have to invite you on this again
and maybe you want to be a contributor
to the the magazine when it comes out
because I would love to hear more you're
you're you are just uh a guy walking
you're walking encyclopedia for for for
um social um influencing and and and
whatnot so thank you so much for coming
on to the show I I got a lot of value
from it and I appreciate the time man
yeah so if you want to come on anytime
you're more than welcome uh so thanks so
much Brandon so
folks if you're coming in late I've seen
this has been I don't understand how you
guys have not you you didn't come in
earlier I see Philip Woods Susan day uh
John John Jensen everyone came in late
so what you're going to have to do is
you're going to have to dial back and
watch this again because this was
actually I wasn't I was just expecting
because you know normally with the
hustle Zone we talk about personal lives
Etc but um you know Brandon came in and
he just gave us facts um and a lot of
key things because even with his book
about crowdfunding and I am going to ask
him what the name of that book is again
so I can go and and and purchase that
book because I think a lot of the things
that he's saying you know I've been
telling my clients for years uh but you
you really got to put in the work when
it comes to internet
marketing and and promotions um and then
crowdfunding I mean the fact that this
guy has made it in crowdfunding a lot of
people cannot say that they have the
same skill set so you definitely most
definitely want to want want to follow
uh Brandon so his links or the link to
his profile is in my description again
we're going to be doing this
consistently at 9: every night we're
just you know I'm just getting
everything set up as you can see like I
had a background earlier but I took the
bra background down because it was
eating up my CPU so I'm just testing out
different things buying equipment and
trying to make this the best show ever
uh but I can't do this without your help